<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Snoogans.co.uk</title><link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on Snoogans.co.uk</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.snoogans.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beginner CFOP</title><link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/cubing/beginner-cfop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/cubing/beginner-cfop/</guid><description>Introduction: When moving from the beginner method to CFOP, I found it overwhelming to learn all the new 2-Look OLL and PLL algorithms.
I discovered that it is possible to reduce the number of 2-Look OLL and PLL algorithms you need to use in order to solve the cube whilst still using the CFOP method.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a semi-decent speed cube, something like the MoYu RS3M 20201 as pictured above, will make cubing so much more enjoyable.</description></item><item><title>Captive</title><link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/stuff/captive/captive.htm</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/stuff/captive/captive.htm</guid><description>Captive game design, programming and graphics by Antony Crowther.
Introduction: The futuristic Dungeon Master in space, with robots and lasers.
When Captive was originally released on the Amiga in 1990 I spent a good deal of my leisure time ploughing through it&amp;rsquo;s alleged 65,536 levels. As far as I could tell the levels were split up into missions, with 11 levels per mission. The final level of a mission being extremely large and introducing some real bad ass monsters.</description></item><item><title>Hosting History</title><link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/hosting-history/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/hosting-history/</guid><description>Introduction: I have hosted snoogans.co.uk for many years.
jay.snoogans.co.uk I built this server using old server parts whilst working at the ISP, Netscalibur.
I was lucky enough to have full access to the datacentre and hosted this for free.
I hosted the webserver via the Apache HTTP Server (&amp;ldquo;httpd&amp;rdquo;) and a full mail server setup running:
Postfix. Cyrus IMAP. Amavisd-new, ClavAV and SpamAssassin. s1.snoogans.co.uk When I left Netscalibur/Claranet, I had to decom jay.</description></item></channel></rss>