<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Snoogans.co.uk</title>
    <link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Snoogans.co.uk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Meta Quest Discounts</title>
      <link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/meta-quest-discounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/meta-quest-discounts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Use my referral links to receive 25% off games and apps. Receive Meta Quest Store credit from new headset purchases.
Devices Buy a new Meta Quest headset from any retailer, and earn rewards once you&amp;rsquo;ve activated your headset.
Get £46 in Meta Quest Store credit for activating the Meta Quest 3 and £23 for the Meta Quest 2 or Meta Quest Pro.
Game/App Discount Offers. Referral/Promo links (25% off) Use my referral links to buy any of these games or apps below and you can get 25% off your purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginner CFOP</title>
      <link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/cubing/beginner-cfop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/cubing/beginner-cfop/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: When moving from the beginner method to CFOP, I found it overwhelming to learn all the new 2-Look OLL and PLL algorithms.
I discovered that it is possible to reduce the number of 2-Look OLL and PLL algorithms you need to use in order to solve the cube whilst still using the CFOP method. This basically turns it into a 3-Look OLL and PLL method.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a semi-decent speed cube, something like the MoYu RS3M 20201 as pictured above, will make cubing so much more enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captive</title>
      <link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/stuff/captive/captive.htm</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/stuff/captive/captive.htm</guid>
      <description>Captive game design, programming and graphics by Antony Crowther.
Introduction: The futuristic Dungeon Master in space, with robots and lasers.
When Mindscape released Captive on the Amiga in 1990 I spent a good deal of my leisure time ploughing through it&amp;rsquo;s alleged 65,536 levels. As far as I could tell the levels were split up into missions, with 11 levels per mission. The final level of a mission being extremely large and introducing some real bad ass monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting History</title>
      <link>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/hosting-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.snoogans.co.uk/posts/hosting-history/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: I have hosted snoogans.co.uk for many years. The website frontend content is very minimal, but I enjoy learning about and configuring the backend.
2002-2004 Netscalibur - Physical server hosting jay.snoogans.co.uk I built this server using old server parts collected whilst working at the ISP, Netscalibur. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the original rear IO plate so made one out of a plastic ice cream container. There were no consumer 3D printers back in 2002.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
